Goodspeed Musicals Scherer Library of Musical Theatre Priority Archive
Goodspeed Musicals
- Inventory
  - Nelson Wheatcroft, undated; Actor Nelson Wheatcroff wearing waistcoat with hands in pocket; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003222 (Box 20*)
  - You Said It, undated; New York; Items: 1; Format: Flyer; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 6 X 9; Barcode: 35111000003347 (Box 20*)
  - Miss Delia Stacey, undated; Actress Delia Stacey; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003370 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Julia Marlow in Romeo & Juliet wearing white dress and black cape; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 5; Barcode: 35111000003461 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Rose Massey, signed on back; Gurney Studios NY; Items: 1; Format: photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003511 (Box 20*)
  - Ida Yearance, undated; Actress Ida Yearance; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 2.5 x 4; Barcode: 35111000003537 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Mary Anderson, in toga w/laurel wreath, Mora Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004105 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Minnie Allen, signed May 1892; J.B. Luttbeg Studios, Mt. Vernon NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.50; Barcode: 35111000004857 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actress-Burton, as "Patience"; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions:; Barcode: 35111000004923 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actor Joseph Jefferson as "Rip Van Winkle"; Sarony, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.50 actual photo missing; Barcode: 35111000005045 (Box 20)
  - No title, undated; Actor Marshall P. Wilder, signed to Mrs. Keller w/Quote"Laugh and the world laughs with you"; Falk Studios NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005474 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Singer Adelina Patti wearing Black dress with white lace scarf and black hat; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005540 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Actor Tommy Russell as "Little Lord Fauntleroy: Litchfield Studios, Boston MA; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.50; Barcode: 35111000005573 (Box 20*)
  - No title, undated; Autographed, star of "She's My Baby"; Items: 1; Format: Photograph; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 8 x 10; Barcode: 35111000006217 (Box 20*)
  - Beatrice Lillie, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; National Theatre, March 1976; Featuring Ken Howard as The President, Patricia Routledge as The President's Wife, and Gilbert Price as Lud; Book & Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner, Music by Leonard Bernstein; Items: 1; Format: Playbill; Page count: 44 pages; Dimensions: 6 x 9"; Barcode: 35111000006662 (Box 21*)
  - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, Stagebill Vol. IV, No. 7, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; An intern's reflections on working with Leonard Bernstein and 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 21 pages; Dimensions: 9.25 x 11.5"; Barcode: 35111000006738 (Box 21*)
  - Reflections on 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; Forrest Theatre; Featuring Ken Howard as The President, Patricia Routledge as The President's Wife, and Gilbert Price as Lud; Book & Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner, Music by Leonard Bernstein; Items: 1; Format: Playbill; Page count: 12 pages; Dimensions: 6 x 9"; Barcode: 35111000008452 (Box 21*)
  - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; Forrest Theatre; Featuring Ken Howard as The President, Patricia Routledge as The President's Wife, and Gilbert Price as Lud; Book & Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner, Music by Leonard Bernstein; Items: 1; Format: Playbill; Page count: 12 pages; Dimensions: 6 x 9"; Barcode: 35111000008460 (Box 21*)
  - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; Mark Hellinger Theatre; May 4, 1976; Featuring Featuring Ken Howard as The President, Patricia Routledge as The President's Wife, and Gilbert Price as Lud; Book & Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner, Music by Leonard Bernstein; Items: 1; Format: Playbill; Page count: 48 pages; Dimensions: 6 x 9"; Barcode: 35111000008478 (Box 21*)
  - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; March 4, 1976; Presented by the Coca-Cola Company for the cast and production crew of "1600 Pennsylvania Avenue"; Held at the Variety Club in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 8 pages; Dimensions: 4 x 5"; Barcode: 35111000008494 (Box 21*)
  - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue Cast Party Invitation, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; Uris Theatre; Featuring Donnie Ray Albert as Porgy, Clamma Dale as Bess, and Wilma Shakesnider as Robbins; Book by DuBose Heywards, Music by George Gershwin, and Lyrics by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin; Items: 1; Format: Playbill; Page count: 62 pages; Dimensions: 6 x 9"; Barcode: 35111000008502 (Box 21*)
  - Porgy and Bess, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; Alam Jay Lerner's tossed lyrics for 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue; Leonard Bernstein's handwritten notes; production schedule from February 14, 1976-February 26, 1976 Revised February 10, 1976; Character-Scene breakdowns; Character list; SATB actor breakdown; Scene-song breakdown; Song list; Outline of the show; 1 Check for $50 to Jim Beloff from the 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue Company 2/12/76; Hotel confirmation for Harrington Hotel in D.C. for the company of 1600 Penn Ave.; Reference request from Jim Beloff (intern) for Leonard Bernstein; Letter from Karen Bernstein, Archivist, to Jim Beloff for providing information on Leonard Bernstein to Springate Corporation's oral-history project; Rough handwritten letter from Jim Beloff to Michael Price; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 43 pages; Dimensions: 5 x 8", 8.5 x 11", 8.5 x 13"; Barcode: 35111000008510 (Box 21*)
  - Miscellaneous Papers from 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Vocal score for 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue; Items: 1; Format: Score; Page count: 291 pages; Dimensions: 11 x 14 x 2.5"; Barcode: 35111000008528 (Box 22 part 1*Part 2*)
  - Vocal Score for 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Jim Beloff's scrapbook of 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue; Items: 1; Format: Scrapbook; Page count: 71 pages; Dimensions: 12.5 x 14.5 x 1.5"; Barcode: 35111000006639 (Box 23*)
  - Scrapbook of 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; Copy of the 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue script; Black cover; Revised copy with new pages, containing a handwritten note stating the following "New Pages. No Pages I-1->4 & I-15 & 16 at the moment…will distribute when definite scene is settled upon! Note: Have gone back to original Jefferson/L.Lud scene. No song-this is probably written in your script anyway!"; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 115 pages; Dimensions: 9.5 x 11.5 x 1"; Barcode: 35111000006647 (Box 24*)
  - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Jim Beloff Collection; Diary of Jim Beloff, 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue Intern; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 152 pages; Dimensions: 7.5 x 12.25 x 1/2"; Barcode: 35111000006712 (Box 24*)
  - Jim Beloff Diary, undated; jim Beloff Collection; Copy of the 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue script; Yellow cover; Items: 1; Format: Script; Page count: 127 pages; Dimensions: 9 x 11.5 x 1/2"; Barcode: 35111000007124 (Box 24*)
  - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, undated; Ziegfeld Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 12 x 9; Barcode: 35111000000954 (Box 25*)
  - Show Boat, undated; Ziegfeld Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 12 x 9; Barcode: 35111000000962 (Box 25*)
  - Rio Rita, undated; Hippodrome spectacular.; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 25; Dimensions: 11 x 9; Barcode: 35111000000970 (Box 25*)
  - Everything, undated; Contains songs, articles about the Hippodrome @1910; Items: 1; Format: Brochure; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 8 x 12; Barcode: 35111000000988 (Box 25*)
  - Hippodrome Souvenir Book, undated; Theatre de Balieff; Items: 1; Format: Souvenir Program; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 9.25 X 12.25; Barcode: 35111000001085 (Box 25*)
  - Chauve Souris, undated; Musical written by Bock and Harnick for New York Worlds Fair 1964-65; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 11 x 8.75; Barcode: 35111000001234 (Box 25*)
  - To Broadway with Love, undated; Program for A Theatre Guild's production, autographed; Items: 1; Format: Souvenir Program; Page count: 18; Dimensions: 9 x 12; Barcode: 35111000001291 (Box 25*)
  - Oklahoma!, undated; Program; Items: 1; Format: Souvenir Program; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 9 X 12; Barcode: 35111000001465 (Box 25*)
  - Student Prince, undated; Program of Shows; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 6 X 12; Barcode: 35111000001911 (Box 25*)
  - Shubert Festival of Musical Comedy - Operetta, undated; Broad Street Theatre, 1881, with music for "Beautiful Snow"; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 12 x 9.25; Barcode: 35111000002117 (Box 25*)
  - Olivette, undated; New York Hippodrome; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 9 x 11; Barcode: 35111000003404 (Box 25*)
  - Hip-Hip-Hooray, undated; Souvenir ProgramBox 25; Items: 1; Format: Souvenir Program; Page count: 36; Dimensions: 9 x 12; Barcode: 35111000017891 (Box 25*)
  - Chu Chin Chow, undated; Souvenir ProgramBox 25*; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 34; Dimensions: 9x 12; Barcode: 35111000017891 (Box No box)
  - No title, undated; Actress Adelaide Prince signed, Sarony Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002356 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Woman in large feathered hat, back is signed "with my love, Florida; March 13th 1898, Washington DC; Items: 1; Format: photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5.25 x 7.25; Barcode: 35111000003131 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Comedienne Verona Jarbeau (signed) Scholl Studios, Chicago; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000003412 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actor Nelson Wheatcroff wearing waistcoat with hands in pocket; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004113 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Bijou Fernandez leaning against hands; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004139 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Grace Golden sitting with hands in lap; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004147 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Rose Coghlan wearing silk dress holding a fan; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004154 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Queenie Vassar- Head Shot wearing white dress and hat; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004162 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Signed 'Julia Vaughan", Mora Studios, NY, 2nd photo signed; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004170 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Lizzie Kelsey, profile in feathered hat, Mora Studio, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004188 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Annie Yeamans holding poison bottle; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004816 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Lillie Langtry- Head Shot wearing flowered hat; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004824 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Comedian Wm. Warren; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 2.5 x 4; Barcode: 35111000004832 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Singer Adelina Patti wearing black dress & hat, white scarf holding a parasol; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004931 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Unknown; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004949 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Ida Mulle, dressed as angel, w/ another angel, Falk Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004956 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Ida Mulle, dressed as angel, w. mirror reflection, Falk Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000004972 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actor Edwin Booth- Head Shot wearing jacket and vest; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005052 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Jeffreys Lewis; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005417 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Ellen Terry as 'Letitia Hardy" in Belle's Stratagem; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005425 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Ellen Terry as 'Beatrice" in Much Ado about Nothing; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005433 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Mary Anderson, in dark gown, hand on cheek, Mora Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005466 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actress Lizzie Webster as Gabriel in Evangeline sitting on couch; Items: 1; Format: Photos; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4 X 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005532 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actor Henry Irving; Samuel A. Walker Photographer, London; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005557 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; 3 performers; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.25 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000005839 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; Actor W.J. Ferguson in black cloak, Sarony Studios, NY; Items: 1; Format: Photo; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 7.50 x 13; Barcode: 35111000005847 (Box 26*)
  - No title, undated; From Oscar Hammerstein, 2nd to Leighton Brill, Dec. 19, 1946, "Show Boat"; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.5 x 7.25; Barcode: 35111000000871 (Box 27*)
  - Hammerstein Correspondence, undated; Oscar Hammerstein to Leighten Brill; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.5 x 7.25; Barcode: 35111000000889 (Box 27*)
  - Hammerstein Correspondence, undated; From Leatrice Zipser (secretary) to Leighton Brill, June 2, 1947, "Show Boat"; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.5 x 7.25; Barcode: 35111000000897 (Box 27*)
  - Hammerstein Correspondence, undated; Letter to Gertrude Folger 5/22/1928; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 3; Dimensions: 5.75 x 7.75; Barcode: 35111000000905 (Box 27*)
  - William Gillette letter, undated; Letter mentions Sunday in the Park with George and Sweeney Todd 5/1994; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.75; Barcode: 35111000000913 (Box 27*)
  - Sondheim Correspondence, undated; Oscar Hammerstein II with Leighton Brill; Items: 23; Format: Letters; Page count: 33; Dimensions: various; Barcode: 35111000000921 (Box 27*)
  - Hammerstein Correspondence, undated; From Oscar Hammerstein to Leighton Brill, April 9, 1948, Audition Dates; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.5 x 7.25; Barcode: 35111000000939 (Box 27*)
  - Hammerstein Correspondence, undated; From Otto Harback to Lewis & Young, Re: "High Jinks", Jan. 1949; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 5.25 x 7.5; Barcode: 35111000001564 (Box 27*)
  - Otto Harbach Correspondence, undated; From Richard Rodgers to Constance Carpenter; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10.5 x 7; Barcode: 35111000001572 (Box 27*)
  - The King and I, undated; From Ira Gershwin to Elizabeth Dickinson, Goodspeed Opera House, 1981; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 11.25 x 8.5; Barcode: 35111000001580 (Box 27*)
  - Gershwin Correspondence, undated; Letter from Marilyn Miller to music director Rabinoff, June 1927; Items: 1; Format: Letter; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 10 x 8.5; Barcode: 35111000001598 (Box 27*)
  - Marilyn Miller Correspondence, undated; Song: New Sun in the Sky, Autographed by Arthur Schwartz; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 9 x 12; Barcode: 35111000001606 (Box 27*)
  - The Band Wagon, undated; Song: Confession, Autographed by Arthur Schwartz; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 9 x 12; Barcode: 35111000001614 (Box 27*)
  - The Band Wagon, undated; Song: Sweet Music, Autographed by Arthur Schwartz; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 9 x 12; Barcode: 35111000001648 (Box 27*)
  - The Band Wagon, undated; Signed by Charles Wakefield Cadman; Items: 1; Format: Sheet music; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 12.5 x 9.25; Barcode: 35111000001663 (Box 27*)
  - At Dawning, undated; Signed by Rudolf Friml Dec. 30, 1943nn; Items: 1; Format: Sheet music; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 12 x 9; Barcode: 35111000001671 (Box 27*)
  - The Donkey Serenade, undated; New Lyrics in Jerry Herman's hand; Items: 1; Format: Lyrics; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 11.25 x 8.75; Barcode: 35111000001853 (Box 27*)
  - Every Time a Cop Falls Down, undated; Piano score bound with thread and cambric. Many corrections.; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 9.25 x 12.25; Barcode: 35111000006654 (Box 27*)
  - Comic Opera Rehearsal, undated; Manuscript and printed conductor score. Bound sewn in cambric and tape.; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 9.5 x 12.25; Barcode: 35111000006670 (Box 27*)
  - Rings on My Fingers - Conductor's Score, undated; Manuscript music bound with glue and reinforced with many labels in the hinge.; Items: 1; Format: Sheet Music; Page count: 3; Dimensions: 9.5 x 12.75; Barcode: 35111000006688 (Box 27*)
  - Comic Opera Rehearsal - Cornet Part, undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017602 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Shenandoah (1974), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017602 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Oh, Lady, Lady (First show at Goodspeed in 1963), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 3; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017610 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Very Good Eddie (1975), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017628 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Oh, Kay (1989), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017636 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Oh, Boy 1964, undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017735 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Sweet Adeline (1977), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 3; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017750 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Going Up (1976), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017644 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Whoopee (1978), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000019244 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - The Five O’Clock Girl (1979), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017651 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Tip-Toes (1978), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017719 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - You Never Know (1964), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017727 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Bloomer Girl (1971), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017669 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - The Red Blue-Grass Western Flyer Show (1977), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017768 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Lady, Be Good (1987), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017685 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Hubba Hubba (1971), undated; Goodspeed Archival Recording; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017693 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)
  - Saturday Night, undated; Reel to Reel Recording of Sondheim singing Saturday Night; Items: 1; Format: Reel to CD; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 4.75; Barcode: 35111000017701 (Box Blck Cab. #2*)